Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
=Gorgeous Dream= (Adapted from the novel "The Charming Evil Consort.")
=حلم رائع= (مقتبس من رواية "الزوجة الشريرة الساحرة").
=Episode 4=
=الحلقة 4=
Father, Mother, I hope you are well.
أبي، أمي، أتمنى أن تكونوا بخير.
May I know why you have summoned I?
هل يمكنني أن أعرف لماذا استدعيتني؟
You forged your household records to infiltrate the Liu Residence.
لقد قمت بتزوير سجلات منزلك للتسلل إلى مقر إقامة ليو.
What was your intention?
ماذا كان قصدك؟
I am slow-witted,
أنا بطيء الفهم
and do not understand what Mother means.
ولا أفهم ماذا تعني الأم.
Come in.
ادخل.
I am Cuixian of the Lianxiang Pavilion.
أنا Cuixian من جناح Lianxiang.
I greet Master Liu and Madam Liu.
أحيي السيد ليو والسيدة ليو.
Is this not my dear sister Si?
أليست هذه أختي العزيزة سي؟
Si.
و.
You are a courtesan,
أنت مومس
yet you dared disguise yourself as a common woman,
ومع ذلك تجرأت على إخفاء نفسك كامرأة عادية،
and entered the Liu Residence as a maid.
ودخلت إلى مقر إقامة ليو كخادمة.
You truly are bold.
أنت جريء حقا.
Master, Madam,
سيدي، سيدتي،
I do not know this woman.
لا أعرف هذه المرأة.
Si,
و،
you changed your name,
لقد غيرت اسمك
and now you pretend not to know your own sister?
والآن تتظاهر بأنك لا تعرف أختك؟
If you had not harmed that patron back then,
لو لم تؤذي ذلك الراعي في ذلك الوقت،
how would I have been dragged down with you,
كيف كنت سأُجرّ معك إلى الأسفل،
beaten until I was covered in wounds?
ضربت حتى أصبحت مغطاة بالجروح؟
Have you forgotten all that?
هل نسيت كل ذلك؟
Get up.
استيقظ.
Father, Mother,
الأب، الأم،
Huan Xi entered the Liu Residence with me after I married in.
لقد دخل هوان شي معي إلى مقر إقامة ليو بعد أن تزوجت.
That makes her one of us.
وهذا يجعلها واحدة منا.
How could you believe the words
كيف يمكنك أن تصدق الكلمات
of someone who slanders without evidence?
من يقذف بلا دليل؟
Master, Madam,
سيدي، سيدتي،
this little wench has a red mole on her shoulder,
هذه الفتاة الصغيرة لديها شامة حمراء على كتفها،
it is what the patrons liked the most.
هذا ما أحبه الزبائن أكثر من غيره.
I will let you all see it now.
سأترككم جميعًا ترون ذلك الآن.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
Young Master Liu, you are here.
السيد الشاب ليو، أنت هنا.
I am Cuixian.
أنا كويكسيان.
Quite lively in here.
إنه مكان حيوي للغاية هنا.
Do you still recall
هل مازلت تتذكر؟
the Si who served you together with me?
من هو السي الذي خدمك معي؟
It is her. Do you recognize her?
إنها هي. هل تعرفها؟
I do not.
انا لا افعل.
Qing.
تشينغ.
Come, have some tea.
تعال، تناول بعض الشاي.
(Huan Xi served in Lianxiang Pavilion with her face veiled.)
(خدمت هوان شي في جناح ليانشيانغ ووجهها مغطى.)
(She should not be recognized.)
(لا ينبغي التعرف عليها.)
Young Master Liu, look.
السيد الشاب ليو، انظر.
The red mole on her shoulder.
الشامة الحمراء على كتفها.
One glance is enough to recognize her.
نظرة واحدة تكفي للتعرف عليها.
Let go.
اتركه.
I recognize it.
انا اعرفه.
I recognize her.
انا اعرفها.
Master, Madam,
سيدي، سيدتي،
you see,
هل ترى،
was I not right?
هل كنت على حق؟
This little wench sneaked into the Liu Residence
تسللت هذه الفتاة الصغيرة إلى مقر إقامة ليو
with ulterior motives.
بدوافع خفية.
It appears that Lou's death
يبدو أن موت لو
has something to do with her.
له علاقة بها.
She is only a maid.
إنها مجرد خادمة.
She could never do all this alone.
لن تتمكن أبدًا من القيام بكل هذا بمفردها.
There must be
يجب أن يكون هناك
someone behind her.
شخص ما خلفها.
All of this
كل هذا
was done by me.
لقد تم ذلك من قبلي.
I am the one who killed Lou.
أنا الذي قتلت لو.
Every one of you in the Liu Residence pretends to be virtuous,
كل واحد منكم في مقر إقامة ليو يتظاهر بأنه فاضل،
yet all of you are filthy and corrupt.
ولكنكم جميعا نجسون وفاسدون.
Hypocrites and venomous snakes.
المنافقون والثعابين السامة
Steeped in wickedness.
غارق في الشر.
And you, drugging yourself, drinking, and playing with women.
وأنت تتعاطى المخدرات وتشرب وتلعب مع النساء.
Steward Chen!
ستيوارد تشين!
- None of you deserve a good end! - Get out!
- لا أحد منكم يستحق نهاية جيدة! - اخرج!
I will do whatever I want.
سأفعل كل ما أريد.
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
Wenyu.
لك.
- Who do you think you are? - Huan Xi!
- من تظن نفسك؟ - هوان شي!
Wenyu.
لك.
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
Shameless creature.
مخلوق بلا خجل.
- Let go. - Are you hurt?
-اترك الأمر. -هل أنت مصاب؟
Tell me, who ordered you to do this?
قل لي من أمرك بفعل هذا؟
Speak.
يتكلم.
Who told you to do it?
من قال لك أن تفعل ذلك؟
Say it. Who was it?
قلها. من كان؟
Speak. Who instructed you?
تكلم. من الذي أرشدك؟
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
Huan Xi, your hand.
هوان شي، يدك.
Get away.
ابتعد.
You foolish woman.
يا لك من امرأة حمقاء.
I used you.
لقد استخدمتك.
I returned solely for revenge.
لقد عدت فقط من أجل الانتقام.
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
I will make every one of you
سأجعل كل واحد منكم
pay for blood with blood.
ادفع ثمن الدم بالدم.
Are you looking for death?
هل تبحث عن الموت؟
Let go of me.
أتركني.
Huan Xi.
هوان شي.
- Let go of me. - Do you want to die?
-اتركني. -هل تريد أن تموت؟
Huan Xi!
هوان شي!
Drag her to the woodshed.
اسحبها إلى مستودع الحطب.
She will be executed at noon tomorrow.
سيتم إعدامها ظهر غدًا
Huan Xi!
هوان شي!
With your kind heart,
مع قلبك الطيب
you will surely save her.
سوف تنقذها بالتأكيد.
Shen Wanqing.
شين وان تشينغ.
Xie Ruilan.
شيه رويلان.
Sir.
سيد.
Please, help me save Huan Xi.
من فضلك ساعدني في إنقاذ هوان شي.
I am leaving soon.
سأغادر قريبا.
(Liu Ma, servant of Qin Moxiu)
(ليو ما، خادم تشين موكسيو)
Please go back.
(ليو ما، خادم تشين موشيو) من فضلك ارجع.
I can help you bring down the Liu Residence.
أستطيع مساعدتك في هدم منزل ليو.
Three years ago, you saved me.
لقد أنقذتني منذ ثلاث سنوات.
It was to forge
لقد كان من أجل تزوير
a blade that could challenge the Lius.
شفرة يمكن أن تتحدى ليوس.
Only by toppling them
فقط بإسقاطهم
can we get close to the truth.
هل يمكننا أن نقترب من الحقيقة؟
I
أنا
am the only one who can break them open from within.
أنا الوحيد الذي يمكنه كسرهم من الداخل.
But your ambitions are too large.
لكن طموحاتك كبيرة جدًا.
I dare not use you.
لا أجرؤ على استخدامك.
We depart.
نحن نغادر.
This…
هذا…
You poisoned me.
لقد سممتني.
It was you who taught me this three years ago.
لقد كنت أنت الذي علمني هذا منذ ثلاث سنوات.
When the enemy is difficult to face,
عندما يكون من الصعب مواجهة العدو،
one must lower oneself,
يجب على الإنسان أن يخفض نفسه،
to strike when least expected.
الضرب عندما لا يكون متوقعا.
You stayed in the Liu Residence these days.
لقد بقيت في سكن ليو هذه الأيام.
You must have something on the Xie family.
لا بد أن يكون لديك شيء عن عائلة شيه.
If you want to live,
إذا كنت تريد أن تعيش،
then tell me.
ثم أخبرني.
You cannot even handle someone like Xie Ruilan.
لا يمكنك حتى التعامل مع شخص مثل شي رويلان.
When you are out in the world, never tell anyone
عندما تكون خارجًا إلى العالم، لا تخبر أحدًا أبدًا
that I trained you.
أنني دربتك.
I only need to deal with you.
كل ما أريده هو التعامل معك.
Master Xie.
المعلم شيه.
Farewell.
وداع.
You are not poisoned.
أنت لست مسموما.
Compared to three years ago,
بالمقارنة مع ثلاث سنوات مضت،
she has gained a sharper edge.
لقد اكتسبت حافة أكثر حدة.
Lan Mengyan.
لان منجيان.
I shall see for myself
سأرى بنفسي
how this blade of yours
كيف هذه الشفرة الخاصة بك
will draw blood.
سوف يسحب الدم.
Useless fool.
أحمق عديم الفائدة.
(Xie Yaozu grew up steeped in male supremacy.)
(نشأ شي ياوزو وهو غارق في سيادة الذكور.)
(Now he must live under his sister's shadow in the Liu household.)
(يجب عليه الآن أن يعيش تحت ظل أخته في منزل ليو.)
(Resentment churns within him.)
(الاستياء يدور في داخله.)
(And he vents it upon the weak.)
(ويقذفه على الضعفاء)
Do you think you are even convincing?
هل تعتقد أنك مقنع؟
Xie Yaozu, you useless fool.
شيه ياوزو، أيها الأحمق عديم الفائدة.
You cannot handle the smallest task.
لا يمكنك التعامل مع أصغر مهمة.
Hurry up and go.
اسرع واذهب.
Continue.
يكمل.
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.
You cannot even manage something so trivial.
لا يمكنك حتى إدارة شيء تافه كهذا.
Continue.
يكمل.
If not for me,
إن لم يكن لي،
what could you ever accomplish on your own?
ماذا يمكنك أن تحقق بمفردك؟
If you gamble again,
إذا قمت بالمقامرة مرة أخرى،
you will crawl out of this house.
سوف تخرج من هذا البيت زحفا.
I will never dare again.
لن أجرؤ على ذلك مرة أخرى.
Sister.
أخت.
At once.
في الحال.
How dare you order me around?
كيف تجرؤ على إصدار أوامر لي؟
I am the only son of the Xie family.
أنا الابن الوحيد لعائلة شيه.
Who do you think you are?
من تعتقد نفسك؟
You are nothing but a stepping stone.
أنت لست سوى حجر عثرة.
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
Xie Zhaodi.
شي تشاودي.
Did you really think a new name could change your fate?
هل كنت تعتقد حقًا أن اسمًا جديدًا قد يغير مصيرك؟
You are nothing but a lowly thing warming Liu Qinghe's bed.
أنت لست سوى شيء متواضع يدفئ سرير ليو تشينغهي.
Do not forget
لا تنسى
your life exists for my sake.
حياتك موجودة من أجلي.
Go on.
إستمر.
Continue.
يكمل.
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.
Without me,
بدوني،
you would have been driven out long ago.
لقد تم طردك منذ زمن طويل.
Useless.
عديم الفائدة.